<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Maddi Anderson&#39;s Site</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Maddi Anderson&#39;s Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Are the Chicago White Sox doomed? Or are they just off to a rough start? </title>
      <link>/2022/04/29/are-the-chicago-white-sox-doomed-or-are-they-just-off-to-a-rough-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/04/29/are-the-chicago-white-sox-doomed-or-are-they-just-off-to-a-rough-start/</guid>
      <description>The Chicago White Sox have been a hot topic for the past few years. After going through a rigorous rebuild, many people are expecting them to win a World Series title in the next couple years. The problem is, the White Sox are currently a “win now” team. They have all the talent they need, but they are struggling to come together as one.
Comparing the 2021 and 2022 seasons is a heartbreaking sight for most fans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Did Nebraska deserve to have a 3-9 season? </title>
      <link>/2022/04/08/did-nebraska-deserve-to-have-a-3-9-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/04/08/did-nebraska-deserve-to-have-a-3-9-season/</guid>
      <description>Nebraska fans are some of the most loyal sports fans on Earth. They have gone through many seasons of victory, and more recently, long seasons of disappointment.
But the 2021 season left many fans asking the same questions; are we really that bad? How are we losing with the talent we have? When taking a deeper look into the tragedy of the 3-9 2021 season, it is evident the Huskers should have pulled off more than a lousy three wins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Maddi Anderson</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! My name is Maddi Anderson, and I am currently a junior at the University of Nebraska-Lincoln. I am studying sports media as well as minoring in business administration. I have always been fascinated with watching sports and storytelling, and found out I can do both of those things through sports journalism. My time at the journalism school is almost up as I graduate in May of 2023, but the things I have learned at my time here so far will last a life time and I cannot wait to use my knowledge in the professional world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
